Guide to the Records of the Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Eleazor Bromberg 1952-1980 RG 6.1 RG 6.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Palisades Institute, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Patents, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - NY Ocean Science Laboratory, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Contracts & Grants Monthly Reports Office of Sponsored Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Office of Institutional Research and Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - NYU Research Services - Roth, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - National Institute of Health, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227192 7
  - NDEA, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - University Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - New Careers Development Center, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Oceanography, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - O, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk State College, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - J, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - All-University Department of Journalism, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Management Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - L, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - I, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Ibero-American Studies, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ICRH, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Institutional Grants Committee, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - International Student Center, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - H.U.D., undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Mathematics, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Leadership Program, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Committee On Minority Group Programs, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Music, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - N, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - NASA Urban Applications Center, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Library, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Libraries, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Linguistics, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - M, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - New Careers Development Center #2, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Graduate Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227193 5
  - H, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - President James M. Hester, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - President James M. Hester, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Hindle, Brooke, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Department of History, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Title 1 - Education Act, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - HUD #2, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Chrono - June, July, August, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Chrono - March, April, May, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Chrono - January, February, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Chrono - September - December, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Chrono, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - All University Department - Anthropology, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Vice President for Administrative Services, 1968-1971 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Vice Pres., General Counsel and Secretary, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Admissions, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Education, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Biology, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Facility, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Annual Community Leadership Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - New York Ocean Science Laboratory, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Affiliated College and Universities, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - All University Departments, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Bronx Community Study, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - The Center for Safety, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Budget Advisory Group, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Budget, 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn Academy, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Commission on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - New York Astronomical Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Dean's Council, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Dean's Council, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Educom, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227194 3
  - Department of Chemistry, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Center for International Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Science Development Proposal, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Computers, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Committee of Deans, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Committee of Deans, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Computers, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Blue Sheets, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Letters (1 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227195 0
  - Miscellaneous Personal Letters (2 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Letters (3 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Personal Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227196 8
  - Humanities Endowment Foundation, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - National Foundation for the Arts & Humanities, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation - Inventory of Computers, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - NSF Traineeships Ad Hoc Committee 9-18-69 - Dr. Robinson, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - NDEA IV NSF Dr. Robinson January 19, 1968, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - English, 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - NSF, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Sloan Foundation, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Sloan Foundation - A Proposal To…, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - G, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Genesys Systems, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Genetics, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Goddard Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Georgiadis File, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Commission, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - The Field Foundation, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Danforth Foundation, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Finance Committee, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Financial Aid, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - The Foundation Center, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Free Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - The Carthage Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Ford Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Ford Foundation - Humanities Research Computer Center at NYU, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Draft, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Easton, Glenn H., Jr., undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Economics, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Enroth, C.E., 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - F, undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Council, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Computer Users Group, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Computers, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Congressional Record, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Coordinating Council for Higher Education, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Ad Hoc - All University Criminological Coordinating Council, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - UCAS Course Evaluation, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227197 6
  - Courses (Fees), 1970 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - D, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Small Deans' Council, 1970-1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Deans' Council, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Development, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Development, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Disciplinary Procedure, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - AAUP, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - American Language Institute, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Colleges, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Association of Urban Universities, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - B, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Biology, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - C, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Center for International Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Center for Safety, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Chemistry, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - College Bowl, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Commission on Effective Use of Resources, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Committee of Deans - Arts and Science, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Committee for Avoidance of Violence, undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Effective Utilization of Faculty Resources, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Senior Fellowship Selection Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - SETE, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - WSC - Faculty Meetings (Minutes), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - GSSW - Faculty Meetings (Minutes), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Chrono - Aug. - December, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Chrono, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - A, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Academic Computing Center, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Accreditation, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Administrative Services - VP Irving Berezin, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Research, undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Ross Professorship, undated (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - S, undated (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Science Development Program (NSF), undated (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Albert Schweitzer Chair in the Humanities, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Science Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Senate Committee on Educational and Organizational Policies, undated (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - SES Faculty Acceptance Letters, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227198 4
  - President's Tea, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Committee Telephone, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - EDP: Priorities Committee, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Committee on Mail Services, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Real Estate (Netzer), undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Student Recruitment (Dean Payne), undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Campus Stores - Subcommittee (Mayerson), undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Student Activities and Services (Griffiths), undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Implementation Committee, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings (Minutes), 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Committee Institutional Facilities, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Dean Winder's Committee on Insitutional Facilitiies and Administrative Services, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Financial and Administrative Controls (Dill Committee), undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Computer Committee (Provost Hyde), undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Publications (Kentera), undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Effective Use of Resources: University Vehicle Evaluation, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Commission on Effective Utilization of Resources, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Dormitories and Dining Halls, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Club - T.O.P. Sub-Committee, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Shuttle Service: WHts-WSq., undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Suggestions on Cost Reduction, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Urban Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Urban Affairs, 0000 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Adhoc Committee Health Services, 19701971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227199 2
  - Replacement Services, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New York University Student Related Systems, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Large Scale Public EDP System: Its Problem and Prospects, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - MIS Committee, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - UCAR, 19701971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Adhoc Committee Health Services, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Callos Manual: background material, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227212 3
  - Cost Allocation Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - EDUCON, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Oberlin Model, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - CUNY/University Computer Center Info, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Cost Accounting, 19771979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Cost Allocation Reports, Section A, 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Cost Allocation Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - 1979-80 Budget Cost Allocation report, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Enrollment, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - notes on data, Re: Admissions Office, 1975-1979 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Admissions versus Enrollment Data from Janes Maggins office, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report Data, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - SEHNAP enrollment projections, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Balance of Trade, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Schools' Enrollment Projections [taken from budget requests], 1979 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - "Al's Tenure Toy": A Demonstration of Non-Financial Capabilities of the EDUCON Financial Planning Model, Nov 1978 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - 1980-1981 Budget (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Public Polict Monograph Series: 1979 Fall Enrollment at Independent Colleges and Universities (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - 1980-1981 Income & Expense Summary (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Dorothy Tonna, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment: misc., 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Attrition Data, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Expenditures, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - "Materials sent to Dave", 1979 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Balance of Trade, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - misc. budget notes, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - ECR - Peter Chapas, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Payroll/Personnel, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Computer Worksheets, undated (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Long Range Planning, undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Long Range Planning, undated (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Long Range Planning, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Enrollment, 1974-1978 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Enrollment, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Enrollment Model, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Hayden Dining and Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227213 1
  - Housing- Statement of Operations, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Bookstore- Statement of Operations, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Dining- Statement of Operations, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Loeb Front Desk, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Computer Services, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Computer Center, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Computer Center Consolidation, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Computer Center, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Task Force, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Task Force 3-Year Budget Projections, all schools, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227214 9
  - General Correspondance, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Applied Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Services, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Center for International Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Center for Safety, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn College of Pharmacy, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Booz, Allen & Hamilton Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor's Correspondace, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Alterations- Arts & Sciences, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Blancher Management Corp., 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Assistant Chancellor for Administration- Burneson, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - WSUC Arts & Sciences, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Task Force, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Task Force, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Cloud 2W I 37 Hazards Code, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Attrition Rates Undergrad School, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Assistant Chancellor for Operations Analysis- N. Roth, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Art Collection, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Budget Advisory Group, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227215 6
  - Budgets, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Chronological Tables, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Review Group, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Budget Worksheets, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Financial Systems, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Budget Information, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Cost Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Cost Accounting, 1973-1975 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Auxiliaries, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226358 5
  - Housing Services, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Campus Stores, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Dining and Catering, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - LOEB Student Center, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - AAUP Salary Study (HEW Forms), 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Salaries, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Tenure, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Booklet, "Employee Contributions to IRA's and Other Pension Plans", Apr 1979 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Early Retirement, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - TIAA-CREF Study on Age 70 Retirement, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1975-1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Social Security, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Master Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Base Budget Review, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - NYU Organization, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Board of Education, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Cost Allocation Worksheets, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Cost Allocation, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - 1980-1981 Budget (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Financial Affairs Committee Meeting, Additional Budget Material, Mar 1980 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report Project, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Computer Information, 1977-1980 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - NYU Press, 1974-1980 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Telephones/Postage, 1972-1980 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Manahattanville, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Reports and Bulletins, Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Reports and Bulletins, Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - University Financial Crisis, 1971-1974 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Staffing (102), 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Balanced Trade, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Points, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Princeton University Report of the Priorities Committee to the President, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Tom Truitt, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Office of the Registrar, Fall Final Reports, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226359 3
  - Registration Notebook for the Academic Year 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Office of the Registrar, Spring Final Reports,Student Enrollment, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Graph Paper, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Weekly Admissions Report, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Other Data on Enrollment, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Admissions Reports, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Registrar, Annual Reports for Acadmic year 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Nellies Charts, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Enrollment and Registration Data, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Enrollment and Revenue Projections, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 1979-1980 Bugdet Model (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Worksheets for 1979-1980 Budget Model (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - EFPM 2 Second Run, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - EFPM 2 First Run, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Worksheet and Data Source, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - 1980-1981 Budget Model (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - EFPM 5 ( Base Year 1980-Allen), undated (Box 42, Folder 18)